whichtestwon.com 2016-04-16

# Privacy Policy - WhichTestWon

If you followed this link, you care about privacy, and we’re glad because we do as well. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we (WhichTestWon LLC, or “WhichTestWon”) collect through our website located at [www.whichtestwon.com](http://www.bounceexchange.com/) (the “Website”), and how we use that information.  If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [customerservice@whichtestwon.com](mailto:customerservice@whichtestwon.com). 

**The Types of Information that We Collect**

We collect two types of information from visitors to our Website: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) is information that may be used to identify or locate an individual and includes email address, telephone number or postal address. We generally don’t collect PII via the Website unless it is provided to us. 

For example, if you purchase our products or services we may request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form.  This includes contact information such as your name, email address, and address, as well as financial information such as a credit card number and its expiration date.  We use this information for billing purposes and to fill orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we also will use this information to contact you.

In addition, if you contact us by email through our Website, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence.  We reserve the right to use your email address and any other PII that you provide to us to respond to your inquiries and to send you marketing materials for our own products and services.  Certain of our uses are non-exhaustively described below.  We will not share your information with outside parties who wish to market other products and services to you.

We also collect non-personally identifiable information via this Website (“Non-PII”) such as the name of your internet service provider, the IP address of the computer or device you are using, the type of browser and operating system that you use, the date and time you access our Website, the website referrer address and other log file information.  We use analytics technology to measure and optimize our site’s performance, including solutions provided by third parties.  Like most websites, our Website uses “pixel tags”, “web beacons”, “cookies” and/or similar tracking technologies that allow us to track the actions of visitors to our Website. We use this information to help us improve our Website and the products, services, applications, content and features that we provide. We reserve the right to aggregate this information with similar data collected from other visitors to the Website for any purpose, including publishing aggregate statistics about our clients and/or Website visitors.  We may also serve cookies from trusted third party partners, for example our email service provider, which hosts our email opt-in offer.  

**Newsletter**

If you signed up for our newsletter, we will send you our regular periodic newsletter along with occasional special announcements — for example if we have a webinar registration deadline, or info on a special offer from a relevant vendor. However, we will never give a third party your email address for the purposes of a ‘blast’.  

**Webinar and Content Signups**

We use third party vendors for webinar registrations and management.  Your interactions with those third parties are governed pursuant to their respective privacy policies.  While we reserve the right to change these vendors in the future, any web forms and webinar management systems will be evaluated for security prior to implementation.

We and any presentation partner(s) or sponsors will have access and permission to contact people who signed up for a presentation.  For example, we’ll email you with a reminder beforehand and a ‘thank you’ afterward, and you may get a separate communication from the event sponsor.  We may also email you on occasion to let you know about other relevant events WhichTestWon is going to host.

**Contact Us Form**

Queries via our Contact Us form are held pursuant to this Privacy Policy. We will endeavor to reply directly to your question or query, and will store your information in our own customer service database in order to keep track of it for the future. 

**Twitter**

If you use the Twitter options on our site to sign up for alerts and/or to send item hotlinks to your circle, Twitter may track your activity. Their Privacy Policy is [here](http://twitter.com/privacy).

**How We May Transfer the Information We Gather to Third Parties**

Generally, we will not disclose the PII that we collect through your use of our Website to unaffiliated third parties.  We reserve the right, however, to provide such information to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform certain services for us, including order fulfillment and Website-related services such as web hosting, to improve Website-related services and features, to perform maintenance services, and to distribute advertisements and other marketing materials on our behalf.  We also reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable information that we collect to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following reasons: (i) to comply with the law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of our Website or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, safety and security of WhichTestWon and its affiliates, employees, our Website visitors, and/or the public.

**Children’s Privacy**

WhichTestWon adheres to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Our Website is not directed at children under the age of 13. If we are made aware that we have received personally identifiable information from someone under 13, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.

**We are Committed to Making Sure Your Information is Protected**

Our physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards meet or exceed current industry standards regarding the protection of the information in our systems.  We also require contractors and outside companies who work with us to adhere to strict privacy standards through their contracts with us.  Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  Consequently, while we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect information in our systems, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and our servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the Website.  Any information that you provide to us is done so entirely at your own risk.

**We Reserve the Right to Update and Revise this Privacy Policy at Any Time.**

From time to time we review this Privacy Policy to ensure that it complies with applicable law.  Consequently, we reserve the right to update and revise this Privacy Policy at any time.  You will know if this Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit to the website by referring to the “Effective Date of Current Policy” date at the top of this page.  Your use of our Website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us from time to time, and you should, therefore, review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms.  

**In the Event We Engage in a Business Combination, We Reserve the Right to Transfer Any Information in Our Systems.**

If we sell all or any part of our business or sell or transfer all or a material part of our assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or other transfer or disposition of any part our business, we reserve the right to access, transfer or disclose any and all information that we collect from our Website’s visitors, or that we otherwise collect in connection with the Website or Platform, to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**Data is Stored in the United States of America.**

Our Website is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Website, you authorize the export of PII to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy. 

**Our Website may Contain Links to Other Websites.  **

Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites that you access through our Website and that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which we collect.  We encourage you to ensure that you read the privacy statements of all the destination websites which you visit.

**Contact WhichTestWon Regarding Our Privacy Practices.**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at (646) 902-4989 or  [customerservice@whichtestwon.com](mailto:customerservice@whichtestwon.com).  We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
